Guide to the Barbara Shailor, Deputy Provost for the Arts, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Barbara Shailor, deputy provost for the arts, records, 1989-2006; Accession 2009-A-120; 16
  - Yale Development Board Meeting, 1999 April 22-23 (Box 9, Folder 491)
  - History of Art Building Committee, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 492)
  - Art Gallery Building Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 493)
  - YDS Building Project, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 494)
  - Fraternity Row, 2002 January 10 (Box 9, Folder 495)
  - History of Art Building Project
    - 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 496)
    - Rudolph, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 497)
    - Building Committee, 2002 February 28 (Box 9, Folder 498)
    - Executive Committee, 2001 May 6 (Box 9, Folder 499)
    - Arts Library Program, 2001 May 30 (Box 9, Folder 500)
    - New building, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 501)
    - Subcommittees, 2001 April (Box 9, Folder 502)
    - AV, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 503)
  - Arts Facilities 2003, 2002 August 12 (Box 9, Folder 504)
  - Sprague Building Project (School of Music)
    - 435 College, 2001- 2002 (Box 9, Folder 505)
    - Sprague, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 506)
    - Campaign/Arts, 1997- 1998 (Box 9, Folder 507)
  - Architecture Building Project
    - Arch/HYA Facilities 2002, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 508)
    - Architecture Facilities 2002 Agreement with SOM (Childs), 2001 October 19 (Box 9, Folder 509)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 510)
    - Architecture Facilities 2001-2002, 2001 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 511)
    - Subcommittees, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 512)
    - Rudolph Building, 2001 May 29 (Box 9, Folder 513)
    - Committee, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 514)
  - Art History Steering and Medieval Search Committee, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 515)
  - UCC Technology, 2000-2003 (Box 10, Folder 516)
  - PEW - Skip, 1998-2002 (Box 10, Folder 517)
  - Music Advising Bd, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 518)
  - Barbara and Susan, 2003- 2005 (Box 10, Folder 519)
  - Barbara's Discretionary, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 520)
  - School of Architecture
    - General, 2002-2003
      - Arch. Travel Reimbursement, 2002 July 12 (Box 10, Folder 521)
      - General Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 522)
      - Salaries, 2002 April - August (Box 10, Folder 523)
      - Leaves, 2002 November 21 (Box 10, Folder 524)
    - Architectural Design, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 527)
    - Architectural Design Search 2003, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 528)
    - 2000-2001
      - Searches, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 530)
      - Computing Position, 2001 August 3 (Box 10, Folder 531)
      - Undergraduate Computer, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 532)
      - Safety Issues, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 533)
      - Ferrucci, 2001 January (Box 10, Folder 534)
      - Visiting Professors, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 535)
      - UDW (Urban Design Workshop), 2001 May - October (Box 10, Folder 536)
    - 5-Year Plan, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 537)
    - Berke - Brooks, 1998-2003 (Box 10, Folder 538)
    - Faculty Guidelines, 1999 December 6 (Box 10, Folder 539)
    - Davenport Professor and Hoppin Professor, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 540)
    - Development
      - Ennis Award, 2002 November 19 (Box 10, Folder 541)
      - Russell Scholarship, 2002 March (Box 10, Folder 542)
      - 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 548)
      - Interim Renovation (Architecture), 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 551)
    - Architectural Design and History/Theory, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 553)
    - Major, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 554)
    - Accreditation, 1993- 2001 (Box 10, Folder 555)
    - 5-Year Plan, 2001 September 14 (Box 10, Folder 556)
    - Executive Committee, 1999 December (Box 11, Folder 557)
    - Moore Exhibition -Architecture General, 2000 May (Box 11, Folder 558)
    - Moore Exhibition Loan, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 559)
    - SFAS/Budget 1999-2001, 1999 January - February (Box 11, Folder 560)
    - IT - Financial Aid, 1998-2002 (Box 11, Folder 561)
    - Financial Aid Study, 2000 October 5 (Box 11, Folder 562)
    - Tuition/Aid, 2000 November 20 (Box 11, Folder 563)
    - Faculty Matters
      - Architecture/Landscape Design, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 564)
      - Axley, 1993- 2000 (Box 11, Folder 565)
      - Junior Searches, 1997- 1998 (Box 11, Folder 567)
      - Design Search, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 569)
      - Visual Studies and Digital Media (Michael Silva), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 570)
      - Building Technology - Junior, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 572)
    - Annual Report Stillwater Long Range Plan, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Material for President, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - Faculty Plan, 1999 October 13 (Box 11, Folder 575)
    - Stillwater Report, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 579)
    - CNTS Fellowship Program, 2002 February 13 (Box 11, Folder 580)
    - Admissions 2003, 2002 January (Box 11, Folder 581)
    - History of Art Searches - Architecture, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 582)
    - Sacred Architecture Luce, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 583)
    - Faculty Appointments/Promotions, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 584)
    - Faculty, 2002-2003
      - 2002-2003, 2002 May 8 (Box 11, Folder 585)
      - Promotions/Appointments, 2002 June 4 (Box 11, Folder 586)
      - Leaves, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 587)
      - Early Retirement, 2002 October 14 (Box 11, Folder 588)
      - Appointments, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 589)
  - Capital Projects 2003, 2002 June 1 (Box 11, Folder 590)
  - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 591 - 592)
  - Managerial and Professional (M & P) Salaries, 2002 May - June (Box 11, Folder 593)
  - Symposia
    - Curie Symposium, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 594)
    - Symposium Invites, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 595)
    - Marie Curie Nobel Centennial Session, 2003 November 12 (Box 11, Folder 596)
    - Marie Curie Nobel Centennial - Friday Session, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 597)
    - Marie Curie, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 598)
    - Invitation Lists, Marie Curie, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 601)
  - Divinity - Lilly - Development 1, 1996- 1998 (Box 11, Folder 602)
  - Divinity - Lilly -Development 2, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 603)
  - Diana's Discretionary, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 604)
  - Meyerhold Project, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 605)
  - School of Drama
    - New Ticket System, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 606)
    - Shakespeare Company, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 607)
    - Faculty, 1998-1999
      - Dramaturgy Search, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 609)
    - Benefit, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 613)
    - Truck, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 614)
    - Drama Appointments, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 615)
    - Dramaturgy, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 616)
  - DMCA Advisory Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 618)
  - DMCA 1998, 1995- 1998 (Box 12, Folder 619)
  - Digital Media, 1997- 1998 (Box 12, Folder 620)
  - University Council - Art, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 621)
  - School of Art
    - 1998 (Box 12, Folder 622)
    - Faculty, Budget, Miscellaneous, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 623)
    - Art School Search
      - Search - Miscellaneous, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 640)
      - Possibilities, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 675)
      - Dean Search, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 677)
  - Music School - Dean Search
    - Nominations and Applications, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 678)
    - Advertisement and Placements, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 679)
  - ISM Search, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 731)
  - Religious Studies Rankings and Divinity School, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 732)
  - Barbara's Research A/C, 2003-2006 (Box 13, Folder 734)
  - Barbara's Discretionary A/C, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 735)
  - Seaver, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 738)
  - Andrew W. Mellon, 2004-2006 (Box 13, Folder 739)
  - Music and Art Search Bills, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 742)
  - ISM Comments Candidates, 2004 November 3 (Box 14, Folder 745)
  - ISM Search Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 746)
  - Research Assistants, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 747)
  - Arts Library, 2003 July 7 (Box 14, Folder 748)
  - Walter Parkes At Yale, 1999 October 14 (Box 14, Folder 749)
  - Day At Yale, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 750)
  - YUAG Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 752)
  - Alliance Town Meeting, 2000-2003 (Box 14, Folder 753)
  - Yale Development Board, 1999 April 22-23 (Box 14, Folder 755)
  - Development Board, 2000 October 27 (Box 14, Folder 756)
  - University Council Meeting, 2001 December (Box 14, Folder 757)
  - History of Christianity Search - Divinity School, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 758)
  - Senior Building Technology, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 759)
  - Old Testament (Seitz Replacement), 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 761)
  - School of Architecture
    - Computing, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 762)
    - Salaries, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 763)
    - Leaves, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 765)
    - Faculty
    - Design Search, 1989 October 3 (Box 14, Folder 769)
  - Institute of Sacred Music
    - Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 775)
    - Buildings, 1997 November 21 (Box 14, Folder 776)
    - Modules, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 777)
    - Margot's Students Tuitions, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 778)
    - Musical Instruments
      - Budget 1996-1997, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 779)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 780)
      - Budget Info, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 781)
  - Music School Salary, 1978-2001 (Box 14, Folder 782)
  - Collection of Musical Instruments, 1986- 1987 (Box 14, Folder 783)
  - Rephann - Appointment Miscellaneous, 1964- 2003 (Box 14, Folder 784)
  - Collection of Musical Instruments, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 785)
  - Rephann
    - Miscellaneous, 1996- 1997 (Box 14, Folder 786)
    - Contracts/Salary, 1975- 2004 (Box 14, Folder 787)
    - Appointment Forms, 1969- 2004 (Box 14, Folder 788)
  - Collection of Musical Instruments
    - 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 789)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 790)
    - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 791)
    - Pre-1984, 1978-1984 (Box 14, Folder 792)
  - Rephann
    - Correspondence, 1983- 2004 (Box 14, Folder 793)
    - Artistic, 2004 April 4 (Box 14, Folder 794)
  - unspecified
    - Divinity School, 1997-2001 (Box 15, Folder 795)
  - Berkeley Gifts, 1971- 2001 (Box 15, Folder 796)
  - Berkeley Audit, 1997-2001 (Box 15, Folder 797)
  - ISM, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 798)
  - Divinity School, 2001 December 11 (Box 15, Folder 799)
  - Berkeley Development, 2001 October 25 (Box 15, Folder 800)
  - Divinity School, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 802)
  - Berkeley Divinity School, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 805)
  - PONPO, 2002 March 15 (Box 15, Folder 806)
  - ISM Search, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 807)
  - Final Report Appendices: Divinity, 1995 October 30 (Box 15, Folder 809)
  - Chron File, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 810)
  - Retirees, 1993-1999 (Box 15, Folder 811)
  - Faculty Salaries Professional Schools 2001-2002, 2001 May - June (Box 15, Folder 813)
  - Budgets, 2003-2004
    - Meeting, 2003 January 10 (Box 15, Folder 814)
    - Drama, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 815)
    - Art Gallery 2004, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 816)
    - DMCA, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 817)
    - Berkeley, 2002 July 10 (Box 15, Folder 818)
    - BAC, 2003 May 27 (Box 15, Folder 819)
    - Architecture, 2003 May 8 (Box 15, Folder 820)
    - ISM, 2003 May 2 (Box 15, Folder 821)
    - Divinity, 2003 June 18 (Box 15, Folder 822)
    - Art, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 823)
    - Music School 2002-2003, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 824)
  - Budgets, 2002-2003
    - Architecture, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 825)
    - BAC 2003-2004, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 826)
    - General 2003, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 827)
  - Yale Center for British Art, 1998-1999
    - Financial Report, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 828)
    - Conservation Committee, 1999 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 829)
    - Advisory Committee, 2000 May 19 (Box 15, Folder 830)
    - Development, 2000 February 28 (Box 15, Folder 831)
  - Chip's Tips, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 832)
  - Women At Yale, 1994-2000 (Box 15, Folder 833)
  - Membership Policies, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 834)
  - Drama Budget 2001-2002, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 835)
  - Faculty Salaries, 2004-2005
    - School of Architecture, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 836)
    - M & P Salaries, 2004 May 11 (Box 15, Folder 837)
    - School of Art, 2004 May 11 (Box 15, Folder 838)
    - Drama School, 2004 September 9 (Box 15, Folder 839)
    - School of Music, 2004 June 21 (Box 15, Folder 840)
    - ISM Faculty Salaries, 2004 June 1 (Box 15, Folder 841)
  - Budgets, 2002-2003
    - DMCA, 2002 January 4 (Box 16, Folder 842)
    - Art, 2001 August 15 (Box 16, Folder 843)
    - Drama, 2002 January - February (Box 16, Folder 844)
    - ISM, 2002 January 30 (Box 16, Folder 845)
    - Gallery, 2002 March 18 (Box 16, Folder 846)
    - Art School, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 847)
    - Divinity School, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 848)
    - 2002 Apr 25 (Box 16, Folder 849)
  - Budgets, 2001-2002
    - Architecture, 2001 February 9 (Box 16, Folder 850)
    - YUAG, 2001 January 20 (Box 16, Folder 851)
    - Art, 2001 May 15 (Box 16, Folder 852)
    - BDS, 2001 December 10 (Box 16, Folder 853)
    - DMCA, 2001 May 16 (Box 16, Folder 854)
    - ISM, 2001 September 9 (Box 16, Folder 855)
    - Music, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 856)
  - Drama School, 1999-2000
    - Budgets, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 857)
    - Capital Requests Budget 1999-2000, 2000 April 24 (Box 16, Folder 858)
    - Dimmers for Yale Cabaret, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 859)
    - Correspondence/Misc, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 861)
    - Acting Position Drama Faculty 1999-2000, 2000 February 1 (Box 16, Folder 863)
  - Salaries, 2003-2004
    - M & P 2003-2004, 2003 June 23 (Box 16, Folder 864)
    - Drama Faculty 2003-2004, 2003 June 5 (Box 16, Folder 865)
    - Art School Faculty 2003-2004, 2003 September 16 (Box 16, Folder 866)
    - Music - Approved Faculty Salaries 2003-2004, 2003 June 18 (Box 16, Folder 867)
    - ISM 2003-2004 Faculty, 2003 November 4 (Box 16, Folder 868)
    - School of Architecture 2003-2004, 2003 August 18 (Box 16, Folder 869)
    - Divinity Faculty 2003-2004, 2003 August 15 (Box 16, Folder 870)
    - Divinity School Faculty 2004-2005, 2004 May 11 (Box 16, Folder 871)
  - Final Report of the Divinity School Committee, 1995 December 5 - 30 (Box 16, Folder 872)
  - Yale University Divinity School Review, 1996 January 29 (Box 16, Folder 873)
  - Yale University Council Committee on the School of Architecture Confidential Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 875 - 877)
- Additional material, 1979-2010; Accession 2015-A-029
  Conditions Governing Access
  No Subnote Content
  - General files
    - Allen, Michael visit, 2008 January 28-29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Philological Association, 1989-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Digital Landscape Feedback, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Franklin papers
      - 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Miami Herald, 2009 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Office of Sustainability annual report, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Urban Studies, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Abu Dhabi
    - Abu Dhabi Music and Arts Foundation (ADMAF) Strategic Vision, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Al Azhar delegation, 2007 March 3-10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Classical Music Festival, 2007 April 17-26 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Concept, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 2007 November 19-2008 February 25 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Miocene fossils-Andrew Hill, 2007 December 7-2008 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Museums proposal, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Music festival, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Program and staffing structure, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 17a)
    - Tourism development and investment company, 2006 August 15-November 30 (Box 1, Folder 17b)
    - United Arab Emirates (UAE) Oman visitors, 2007 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Visit
      - 2006 November 29-30 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - 2007 July 16-17 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Yale Institute of the Arts in Abu Dhabi pre-proposal, 2006 September 17-October 6 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Yale Institute of the Arts in Abu Dhabi-proposal, 2007 May 10-31 (Box 1, Folder 21a)
  - Architecture
    - Archive program at Yale, 2003 August 13-2004 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Associate professorship, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Auditing, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Building Technology Search Committee-document of qualifications, 2006 May 1-31 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Charitable gift annunity, 2004 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Hilles scholarship, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Planning vision, 2001 September 25 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Report of the Building Technology Search Committee and Supplementary Materials, 2006 May (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Classics department
    - General files, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Budget
      - 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Proposal, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Development, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Diversity appointments, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Faculty, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Faculty issues
      - 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Faculty leaves
      - 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Faculty searches, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Greek art search appointment, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Junior Latinist search appointment, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Junior search appointments, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - New appointment policy elections, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Research grants, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Review, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - SWOT evaluation statistics, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Divinity school
    - General files
      - 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Affiliation agreement, 1985-1997 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Alumni directory, Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Assessments, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Audit, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
    - Auditing financial statements and supplementary information, 1997 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 2002 September (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Budget issues, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Centers, 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Convocation booklet, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence-general, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Dean search, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Development Committee, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Financial management, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Indentures, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - License, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - New home on Sterling Divinity Quadrangle, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Occupancy agreement, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - President budget letter, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Rector position, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Salaries, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Space, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Drama, School of
    - Alumni affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Complex, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Dean/Business Managers, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Development, 1998-2005 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Director: Bill Reynolds, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - New asks, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Promotions, 2007-2009 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Report on international activities, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Rockefeller gift, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Survey and recommendation for space, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Spatial analysis, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Trach gift, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Y payments, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Yale essentials, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Machu Picchu
    - General files, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Agreements, 2006 February 24 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Attorney work product, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Catalog entires, 2008 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Court case, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Director: Roger Colten, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Facilities and accreditation, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Follow-up meeting, 2007 March 20-23 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Independent article, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Inventory of museum, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Inventory verification, 2008 March 3-12 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Invoices, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Journalist visit, 2008 June 9-12 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Media tour, 2008 June 9-12 (Box 3, Folder 21-21a)
    - Meeting, 2007 September 14 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Meeting notes, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Memorandum de entendimiento, 2007 September 14 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - News coverage, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Peruvian visit, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Peruvian press visit, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Press, 2007 June 24-2008 April 21 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Publicity, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Reparations request, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Scientific expedition collections, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Talking points, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Time tables and reports, 2007 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Visit, 2008 February 28 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Music, School of
    - Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Collection of musical instruments
      - General files
        - 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 36)
        - 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Advisory Board meeting, 2005 June 29 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Audit report, 1990-2003 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Director Plantiga, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Storage of instruments, 2002-2005 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Then and Now, Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Faculty self-studies, 2007 September 11 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Inventory, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Music development
      - General files, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Adams gift, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Simeone scholarship, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Yale Journal of Music Theory, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk Summer Program
    - General files
      - 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 5 year plan, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Annual report, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Director: Paul Hawkshaw, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 2005-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Map, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Meetings, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Professorships
    - Riggs Professorship, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Scully Visiting Professorship, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Kahn Professorship, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Religious Studies
    - Faculty, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Faculty leaves of absence
      - 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 12a)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Advanced Study of Religion, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Office assistant request, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Skip Stout grant for the study of American religion, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)